ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ernst and Whinney, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  1978 and 1979 Audited financial statements
- Excello, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Showdown In Dixie, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  Article regarding J.P. Stevens; English and German
- Engineering Department, 1977-1980 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  Applications to; Reports from; Memos; Maintenance Records
- Executive Health, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  "Executive Health" Newsletters
- F Misc, 1977-1980 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  Memos; Letters; Reports; Newspaper Clippings; Publications
- Farah Manufacturing Co., 1975-1980 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  Memos; Payment requests; Newspaper Clippings
- Federation of Inter-American Textile, Leather & Garment Workers, Mexico, 1974-1980 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  Memos; Letters; Jacob Sheinkman
- Film Material, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  Memos regarding creation of short educational films; Jacob Sheinkman
- Finance Department, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  Funding/Salary/Expenses Memos
- Murray Finley Memorial Dinner, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  May 4, 1980; Memos and letters discussing Dinner; Photographs of Dinner; Guest and Pledge lists
- Ella Baker Film, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  Grand request; Memos; Letters
- Foreign Firms, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  Newspaper Clipping regarding firm's avoidance of unions; Jacob Sheinkman
- Friedrich-Ebert Foundation, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  Letters between Kristian Mulller-Osten and Jacob Sheinkman
- Frontlash, 1974-1978 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  Frontlash Voting registration Organization; Memos; Letters; Reports; Pamphlets
- Full Employment Action Council, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  Letters; Newsletters from FEAC
- Funds for Human Rights, Inc., 1978 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  Requesting Jacob Sheinkman serves as council member; October 26, 1978
- G Misc, 1978-1980 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  Notes; Memos; Letters; Carpet samples
- Gant Shirtmakers, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  Plant closing announcement; Union response June 11-13
- General Executive Board: Dues Committee., 1980 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  Proposed dues increases, February 20
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  Resolutions passed (telephone poll) June 18 and 30, July 9
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  Resolutions, May 30
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  Notice of board meeting, May 5
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  Memos regarding May 5 meeting
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  Memos; Reports; Newspaper clippings leading up to February 25-29 meeting
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  April 21 memo regarding April meeting
- Department Heads Meeting, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  Memos regarding February 29-March 2 meeting
- General Executive Board: Dues Committee, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  Remarks; Reports, August 1980
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  August 1980 meeting; agenda; minutes; report on previous meetings; memos regarding the meeting
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  Memos and reports regarding political funding and activities for August 1980 meeting
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  Newspaper clippings; ECS & Shilling reports for August 1980 Meeting
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  Research reports and materials for August 1980 meeting
- General Executive Board, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  Pending correspondence, prior to August 1980 meeting
- General Executive Board meeting, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  Agenda; Minutes; Reports; Memos for October 1979
- General Executive Board: Resolutions, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  January 1980
- General Executive Board, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  Resolutions, August 1979
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  Minutes of June 1979 meeting
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  Agenda; Memos; Reports; Resolutions of May 1979 meeting
- General Executive Board-Research Info, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  Reports for February 1979 meeting
- General Executive Board, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  Agenda and Newspaper clippings for February 1979 meeting
- Department Heads Meeting, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  Memo regarding March 1979 meeting
- General Executive Board, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  Jurisdiction memos, March 1979
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  Minutes; Memos; Reports, August 1978
- General Executive Board: Administratorship, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  Memos regarding appointments to; Revocation of; Status of
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  Minutes; Reports; Resolutions; Memos regarding September 1978 meeting
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  Memos; Reports; Agenda; Minutes; Audits regarding June 1978 meeting
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  Memos; Minutes; Agenda; Research reports for March 1978 meeting
- British-North American Committee, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  Memos; Reports, Letters: Research; Invitations; Newspaper clippings
- British-North American Committee. [Folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  Memos; Reports; Letters 1979
- British-North American Committee. [Folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  Memos; Research Reports. 1979
- British-North American Committee, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- British-North American Committee, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- C miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  Memos; Letters, etc
- Canada, 1976-1980 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  Research and Economic reports, Memos, Letters,
- Canada-Newspaper, 1975-1980 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  Clippings and Articles involving unions in Canada
- Canadian-American Committee, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  Memos; Letters; Reports; Research
- Canadian-American Committee, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  January-June 1980; Research; Reports; Memos; Minutes
- Canadian-American Committee, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  Research; Reports; Memos; Letters; Meeting minutes
- Canadian-American Committee, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  General Correspondence; Reports; Research; Meeting notifications
- Canadian clothing negotiations, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  Proposed changes to existing contract; French and English language
- Jimmy Carter, 1976-1980 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, Newspaper clippings
- Canadian Conference, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  Second biannual; correspondence; reports, clippings; June 18-June 20
- Carter/Mondale Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  Correspondence
- Cavalier Clothing, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  Memo regarding, December 4
- Census - N.Y. State, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  Letter and Speech from Mario Coumo
- CETA, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  Comprehensive Employment and Training act
- China Trip, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  Planning; writings; Reports; Memos; Letters, April 12 to April 20
- Citizens Action on Crime, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  Communications
- Citizens for the Constitution, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Citizens/Labor Energy Coalition, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  Materials, Research reports; Communications
- Citizens/Labor Energy Coalition, 1978-1979 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  Materials; Communications; Research reports; Focus on "Big Oil"
- Clippings, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  Newspaper/Magazine clippings,
- Clippings. [Folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  Newspaper clippings related to labor topics
- Clippings. [Folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  Newspaper clippings
- Clothing Manufacturer's Association, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  Communications; Reports; Letters of the CMA
- Clothing Negotiations, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  Memos; Correspondence regarding 1980 negotiations
- Clothing Negotiations Insurance Committee, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  Memo, August 28
- Clothing Negotiations Pension Committee, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  August 28 Memo
- Clothing Negotiations clippings and CMA reports, 1978-1980 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  News clippings and reports ranging from 1978-1980, regarding 1980 negations
- Clothing Negotiations: Clofund Insurance. [Folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  Reports; Memos; Letters
- Clothing Negotiations: Clofund Insurance. [Folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  Actuarial and other reports; memos; letters from Martin E. Segal company
- Clothing Negotiations: Clofund Insurance/Retirement, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  Contains 10 subfolders
- Clothing Negotiations Comparison Figures, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  Memos, reports from Harry Lautman/Economic consulting service
- Clothing Negotiations-Clothing settlement, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  Correspondence; Agreements
- Clothing Negotiations-Clothing Vice Presidents, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  Memos regarding who will negotiate and when negotiations will occur
- Clothing Negotiations-Correspondence, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  Memos; Letters; Reports
- Clothing Negotiations-Financial and Economic Date, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  Clothing Manufacturers Association
- Clothing Negotiations-Research Department Material, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  Economic Consulting Services Reports; Memos; Newspaper Clippings
- Cluett/Peabody, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  Memo and report regarding importations from China, July 9
- Coalition of Labor-United Women, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  Memos, reports, agendas and program for convention
- Commerce Department, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  Report regarding footwear; Correspondence
- Committee to F.R.E.E. New York, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  Information regarding F.R.E.E. N.Y; Letters from John Dyson to Jack Sheinkman
- Communications Workers of America, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  Communications between CWA and Sheinkman; Newspaper clippings
- Con Edison, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  Memos regarding Con Edison power rate increase
- Cone Mills, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  Reports, Memos, Newsletters regarding Cone Mills organizing
- Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  Letters and reports from State Department to Jack Sheinkman
- Consumer Assembly, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  Invitation; Report; Letters; Photograph of January 30 meeting
- Contributions-General, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  Outgoing from Union
- Contributions-General, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  Outgoing from union
- Contributions-General, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Contributions-Political, 1977-1979 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  Contains photograph
- ACWA-Joint Board Toronto, 1973-1980 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  Newspaper Clippings; Communications between Jack Sheinkman and Sam Fox; Memos, Event Programs
- Western Central Joint Board, 1974-1978 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  Communications; Expense Reports
- Joint Boards West Coast Region, 1974-1979 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  Memos and other communications; Newsletter (with Spanish); 1974 Constitution
- Western Joint Board: Ontario, 1975-1980 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  Communications; Reports; Financial statements and audits 1975-1979
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  Financial statements; Memos; Letters from July-December
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  May-July, Memos; Letters; Reports; Statements
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  Research reports; Communications; October 1979-May 1980
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  March 1980; Correspondence and Financial Reports
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  Communications; Financial reports, January-February 1980
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  October-December 1979; Memos; Financial Reports and Authorization requests
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  June-October 1979; Meeting minutes; Financial Reports; Communications
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  Communications, Organizational overview, Financial records, Authorization requests; June
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  Reports; Applications; Communications; Research and Development report, Financial reports; May 1979
- Robert M Dale, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  "Technological Breakthrough to Survival" May 25 1977
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  Reports; Communications April 1979
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  Communications; Financial Statements and Enrollment reports; Meeting Agenda; January-March 1979
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  Communications; Meeting reports; Research Reports by Abernathy; January 1980
- CETA, 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  Use of funds to train workers on sewing machines
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  Cotton Industry Training program
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  Communications regarding Sewing Machine Operators, CETA changes ILGWU
- Joint Job Training and Research, Inc, 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  Sewing Machine Operators; Communications regarding CETA changes; Reports
- Joseph and Feiss Company, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  Communications; Pamphlets
- K miscellaneous, 1975-1980 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  Communications between Jack Sheinkman and others; other correspondence
- Martin Luther King Center for Social Change, 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  Correspondence between Jack Sheinkman and the Center
- Kissinger Meetings, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  News clippings; Reports; Articles about Jewish/Israel issues
- Klimist, McKnight and Sale. P.C., 1979 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  FLI memo and recommendations
- L Miscellaneous, 1973-1980 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  Various Correspondence, Reports, Invitations.
- Labor Advisory Committee for Trade Negotiations and Trade Policy, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  Letter to Jacob Sheinkman, October 10
- Labor Committee for Carter/Mondale, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  Press conference handouts
- Labor/Environment Conference, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  Memos/Reports regarding NYC water supply and new subway tunnels
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  Memos; Carnegie quarterly, Un nuevo dia. (Spanish)
- Labor Legislation, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  Memos; Newsletters; Newspaper clippings
- Labor Policy Advisory Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  Correspondence; Reports
- Labor Coalition for International Trade, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  Briefing Memo, October 6-7
- Labor Unity, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  News clippings; Correspondence
- Leadership Conference, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  Pamphlets, Articles; Reports June 10-12
- Leadership Conference, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  Springfield, June 9-12
- Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  Memo from Arnold Anderson; June 30
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1973-1980 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  Correspondence; Meeting Minutes; Newspaper clippings
- League of Woman Voters of the United States, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  Newsletters; Pamphlets; Correspondence
- Legislation: Various Reports, 1975-1982 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Legislation: General Correspondence - Legislative Department, 1977-1982 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  Donation Recipient lists; Correspondence
- Legal Department, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  Memos; Recommendations; Billable Hours
- Legal Department, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  Memos; Contracts
- Legislative and Political Department, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  Campaign records, Communications to Legislative Officials
- Legislative List, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Lehrman Institute, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  Member booklet, Proposal
- S.D. Leidesdorf, 1975-1978 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  Memos; Reports; Press releases regarding S.D. Leidesdorf Accounting
- Levi-Negotiations, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  Pay rate notes September 1
- Levi-Strauss, 1972-1979 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  Company Info, Organizing, Negotiations, Contracts
- Levi Organizing Campaign, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  Information on union presence; Handout
- Lo Biondo, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  Letters between Biondo and Jacob Sheinkman
- Locals: General, 1976-1980 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  Tax forms; Insurance Memos; General correspondence
- Local 4 ACWA, 1973-1980 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  Financial statements, Correspondence; 1961 Agreement
- Local 88, 1973-1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  Union Manual; Correspondence; Member list
- Local 169, 1973-1980 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  Correspondence; Financial Statements; Reports
- Local 177, 1973-1975 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  Financial Statements; Member List; Correspondence
- Local 324, 1972-1980 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  Financial statements; Accounting; Meeting minutes; Agendas; Reports; Correspondence
- Local 340, 1955-1980 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  Audits; Financial Statements; Correspondence; Pension/Retirement discussion
- Local 340, 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  Disability report; Correspondence
- Local 459, 1974-1977 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  Correspondence; Agreements; Contracts
- Londontown, 1973-1980 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  Legal discussion; Agreements; Correspondence; Internal Memos
- M miscellaneous, 1972-1980 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  Correspondence; Newspaper clippings; Advertisements; Donation records
- Machine Printers and Engravers Association, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  May 28, 1980 Reporting 1979 Financial statements
- Made in U.S.A., 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  Correspondence; Memos; Reports relating to "Made in U.S.A." miniseries on labor history
- Majority Congress Committee, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  September 26; Correspondence
- Manhattan Shirt Company, 1973-1980 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clippings; Financial records; Correspondence; Reports
- Mann Manufacturing, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  1974 Charge against employer
- Manpower Training, 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  Department of Labor and Commerce communications regarding sewing training; Newsletter; News clippings
- Marman Sportswear, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  Correspondence; Insurance payments
- Harold Mayer Productions. Inc., 1973-1977 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  "The Inheritance"; Reports by Mayer; Correspondence
- McBride Team, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  Contributions to.
- McGill study on Amalgamated Retirement fund/Insurance/Pension; Comments on same, Securities reports, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  on Amalgamated Retirement fund/Insurance/Pension; Comments on same, Securities reports; GNMA
- McGregor, 1973-1979 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  Collective Bargaining Agreement; Import reports; Correspondence; Internal Memos; Agendas
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1974-1978 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  Newsletter; Catalog; Reimbursement requests
- J.S. Mediator, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  Correspondence to Jacob Sheinkman regarding mediation
- Memos-General, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  Memos; Newsletters; Flyers
- Memos, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  Reports; Event Schedules; Memos
- Midwest Mutual Insurance Company, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  Correspondence regarding legal service plan, July 25
- Migratory Workers, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  January 7; Memo regarding
- Military procurement, 1974-1977 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  Government Wool procurement; Correspondence
- Minimum Wage, 1973-1977 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  News clippings; Lobbying efforts; Reports; Pamphlets; Memos; Correspondence
- Minimum Wage-Puerto Rico, 1974-1977 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  Committee results; Memos
- Multilateral Trade Negotiations. [Folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  Documents and Reports relating to MTN
- Multilateral Trade Negotiations. [Folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  Documents; Reports; Memos; Data relating to MTN
- Multi-Plant Employers, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  Contract information-with who, when it expires
- Munsingwear, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  Communications with Mungsingwear; Internal Memos regarding.
- N General/Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  Correspondence and Reports regarding Social Justice; Labor Film Festival; Memos; NAACP
- National Committee for Full Employment, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  Agenda; Correspondence
- (The) National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  Wlhelm Weinberg Seminar agenda; Cox/Ruby Luncheon; Correspondence
- National Coordinating Committee for Multi-Employer Plans, 1977-1980 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  Committee Correspondence; Reports
- national Council of Senior Citizens, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  Correspondence; 1981 Progress Report
- National Endowment for the Humanities, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  April 18 Letter
- National Union of Hosiery and Knitwear Workers, 1973-1978 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  Address; Correspondence; Memos
- National Health Insurance, 1974-1979 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  Reports; Articles; Correspondence regarding a NHI plan
- National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, 1973-1981 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- National Union of Textile, Garment, and Leather Workers, 1978-1980 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  Correspondence; relating to Israel
- National Urban Coalition, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  Daily News, July 19
- National Urban Energy Cooperative, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  Articles of Incorporation, Correspondence
- NYC Central Labor Council, 1975-1980 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  Report on 1975 Crisis; 1980 Correspondence
- New York State Economic Advisory Council, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  Research and Policy Reports; Newspaper clippings
- New York State Retirement Fund, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  Correspondence, Report Relating to Atlanta Apparel Manufacturing
- New York University, 1975-1981 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  Correspondence; Awards regarding NYU Labor conferences
- N.O.S.A, 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  Petition against imported leather apparel, correspondence
- National Textiles Recruitment and Training Program, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  Trip Report; "Profiles of Growth"
- Nuclear Power America, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  Reports; Correspondence
- O miscellaneous, 1976-1980 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  Various Reports; Correspondence; Documents
- Office Management; Goldstein, Bourne, 1978-1980 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  Meeting preparation; Correspondence
- Office Unity, 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  Memos regarding, Newsletters
- Open Society Fund, 1975-1979 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  Donations from Union; Correspondence
- Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  Correspondence; Publications
- United States Youth Council Labor Desk, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  Newsletter, Donations from union; Correspondence
- United Steel Workers of America, 1975-1980 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  I.W. Abel Tribute; Correspondence
- United Textile Workers, 1976-1980 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  Newsletter; Correspondence
- United Shoe Workers, 1977-1980 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  Correspondence, Memos, meeting minutes, audit reports, merger agreements
- United Shoe Workers, 1976-1979 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  "United Shoe Worker" publication, other newspaper clipping and articles. Contains set of photographs
- Urban Community Insurance Co., 1980 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  Meeting minutes; Proposals; Financial Statements; Correspondence
- Urban Community Insurance Co., 1979 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  Financial Statements; Reports; Correspondence
- V miscellaneous, 1973-1980 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  Benefits; Reports; Other Correspondence
- Vesting, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  September 17 report on Statutory vesting of benefits
- ACWA: Voting and Ratification, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  Correspondence regarding
- Wage and Price Standards (Carters), 1976-1980 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  Reports; Agreements; Correspondence; Memos regarding
- Wonderknit, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  Contract; Wages; Pension; Seniority proposals; Correspondence
- Worker's Compensation, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  Legislation support; Memos; Reports